# Afonso Pinto

Sintra, Lisboa +351 912 008 773 Afonso.pinto2710@hotmail.com



## **Short introduction**

Hi, my name is afonso and I am a Full stack Developer.

Developing since 2018. Finished a technical course of Management and programming of computer systems in 2021 and since then I have been working as a Full stack developer. Today I can say that I have already deployed two webapps that have multiple users every day. I also develop some automations in python, just to make my life easier either at work or home.

## **Education**

## LEVEL IV TECHNICAL COURSE | 2021 | ESCOLA SECUNDÁRIA LEAL DA CÂMARA

· Management and programming of computer systems

## **Experience**

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER | WEB & GAMBLE | MAY 2021 - JULY 2021

Development of a webapp that manages company data and creates bills.
 Technologies used: PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS

## WEB DESIGNER | DIGITAL XPERIENCE | OCTOBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Design of websites with WordPress and CSS.
 Technologies used: WordPress, CSS, Elementor

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER | FEGIME | JANUARY 2022 - TODAY

- Development of a .Net web application for data control and visualization.
- Management of company data
  Technologies used: C#, .NET, SQL, SAP, VueJS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS